Guide to the Atomic Scientists of Chicago Records 1943-1955
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Subject Matter Files
  - Organizations, FAS, administrative committee, elections (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Organizations, FAS, Committee for Foreign Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Organizations, FAS, Committee on Secrecy and Clearance (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Organizations, FAS. Constitution, amendments (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Organizations, FAS, constitution (new) and by-laws, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Organizations, FAS, misc. correspondence, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Organizations, FAS, council delegates (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Organizations, FAS, council meetings (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Organizations, FAS, dues, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Organizations, FAS, finances (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Organizations, FAS, membership and organizations (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Organizations, FAS, memos from R.L. Meier, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Organizations, FAS, memoranda, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Organizations, FAS, memoranda, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Organizations, FAS, memoranda, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Organizations, FAS, miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Organizations, FAS, newsletters (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Organizations, FAS, news releases (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Organizations, FAS, publications editor (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Organizations, FAS, Scientists' Committee (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Organizations, FAS, Brookhaven Association of Scientists, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Cambridge Scientists (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Organizations, FAS, Chicago Association of Scientists and Engineers, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Scientists of Cornell University (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Organizations, FAS, Dayton Association of Atomic Scientists (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Eastern Iowa Scientists (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Los Alamos Scientists (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Manhattan Project Scientists (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Organizations, FAS, Mohawk Association of Scientists and Engineers, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of New York Scientists, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 12-13)
  - Organizations, FAS, Northern California Association of Scientists (Box 16, Folder 14-15)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Oak Ridge Engineers and Scientists, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Pasadena Scientists (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Philadelphia Scientists (Box 17, Folder 5-6)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Pittsburgh Scientist (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Organizations, FAS, Association of Portland Scientists (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Organizations, FAS, Washington Association of Scientists (Box 17, Folder 9-10)
  - Organizations, FAS, Wisconsin Association of Scientists (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
  - Organizations, National Committee on Atomic Information (NCAI), bulletins (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Organizations, NCAI, committee meetings and policy (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Organizations, NCAI, letters, general (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Organizations, NCAI, newsletters and releases (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Organizations, NCAI, reports on activities (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Organizations, Office of Inquiry into the Social Aspects of Atomic Energy, University of Chicago (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Polls and questionnaires, FAS ballots (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Polls and questionnaires, by-laws and amendments number 1, votes on (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Polls and questionnaires, by-laws and amendments number 2, votes on (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Polls and questionnaires, atomic bomb and world affairs survey, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Polls and questionnaires, membership questionnaires (will speak) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Polls and questionnaires, membership questions (won't speak) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Polls and questionnaires, military control, poll on (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Polls and questionnaires, public opinion, polls on (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Polls and questionnaires, Sacher Poll (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Polls and questionnaires, security clearance correspondence, poll on, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - Polls and questionnaires, Wallace letter (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Polls and questionnaires, World government poll (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Publicity, newspaper (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, public relations (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Publicity, on Senate hearings (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Publicity, press conference held June 22, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Publicity, press release (J. Arnold), June 2, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Publicity, press releases, miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Publicity, radio (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Publicity, U.S. Atomic Energy Commission press releases (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Releases to members, Biological Warfare, National Defense Establishment (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Releases to members, "Come-on" letter (re amendments to AEC procedures) (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Releases to members, meeting notices, memos, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Releases to members, memo sent to ASC members re National Science Foundation Bill, HR 4846 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Speakers' Bureau, Adult Education Council (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Speakers' Bureau, lectures given (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Speakers' Bureau, miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Speakers' Bureau, other sites (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Speakers' Bureau (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Speakers' Bureau, speaker requests, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Speakers' Bureau, speeches given (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Speakers' Bureau, speeches refused (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Speakers' Bureau, speeches requested (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Tax Status, incorporation papers (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Tax Status, income tax returns, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Series II: Correspondence
  - Advertising Council (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Adult Education Council (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - American Association for the United Nations (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - American Association of Scientific Workers (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Americans United (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - American Veterans' Committee (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "A" Associations (Associations of scientists, correspondence, near-print material) (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Association for International Atomic Control (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Association of Industrial Scientists (California) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Associations, British (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Associations, Canadian Association of Scientific Workers (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Associations, Holland (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Atomic Bomb, general booklet correspondence (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - The Atomic Bomb, booklet sent, no charge (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Atomic Bomb, large order correspondence (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - The Atomic Bomb, copy sent for comment (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "B" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "C" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Central Press Clipping Bureau (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Daily News (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Technical Societies Council -SCI-EN-TECH News (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Colgate University (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Columbia Radiation Laboratory (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Study of the Soviet Union (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "D" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Dewey, Bradley Report, correspondence with George Biderman (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "E" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Encyclopedia Yearbook (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "F" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Foreign correspondence, National Sponsors Committee for (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - "G" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - General materials committee correspondence (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - "H" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "I" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Independent Citizen's Committee (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Independent Voter's League (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - International Council of Scientific Unions (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - International Film Foundation (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - International organizations, organizations to further world government ideas (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - International organizations, Students for World Federal Government (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - International organizations, United World Federalists (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - International organizations, United World Federalists of Chicago (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - International organizations, Usborne Plan (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - International organizations, World Government News (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - "J" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "K" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - "L" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Libraries (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - "M" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Magazines (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Mayer, M.G. (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Merriam Lectures, Walgreen Foundation (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, A-H, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, I-P, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Q-Z, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, Old (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Mc" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - McGraw-Hill Publishing Company (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - "N" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - National Conference (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - National Emergency Committee for Civilian Control of Atomic Energy (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - National League of Women Voters (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - National Liaison Committee on Atomic Energy (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - New York Sun (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "O" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - One World or None (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Oram, Harold (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Owens Radio Contact (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "P" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Personnel (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Post War Council (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Printing bids (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Public Administration Clearing House (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - "Q" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - "R" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Readers' Digest (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Reports--Washington (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Rich, Joseph E. (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - "S" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Saturday Review of Literature (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Science Service (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Simpson correspondence, Washington (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Simpson's reports (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Szilard article, "Atomic Bombs and the Post War Position of the United States in the World", and correspondence (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - "T" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Telegrams (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "U" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - United Nations Atomic Energy Commission (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - University of California (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - University of Chicago (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Urey (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - "V" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - "W" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - We The People (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - "X-Y-Z" miscellaneous correspondence (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Series III: Library of the ASC
  Series III, Library of the Atomic Scientists of Chicago, includes correspondence, scripts, near-print material, etc. relating to work of the ASC.
  - Atomic Scientists of Chicago, August-September, 1945 (Box 26, Volume 1)
  - Atomic Scientists of Chicago, October-November, 1945 (Box 26, Volume 2)
  - Atomic Scientists of Chicago, December, 1945; 1946 (Box 26, Volume 3)
  - Atomic Scientists of Chicago, miscellaneous (Box 26, Volume 4)
  - Federation of Atomic Scientists (Box 26, Volume 5)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 26, Volume 7)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations, Britain, Clinton, Los Alamos (Box 26, Volume 8)
  - National Committee on Atomic Information (Box 27, Volume 9)
  - Independent Citizen's Committee of the Arts, Sciences, and Professions (Box 27, Volume 10)
  - Miscellaneous Independent Statements on Atomic Energy (Box 27, Volume 11)
  - Lectures (Box 27, Volume 12)
  - Radio broadcasts (Box 27, Volume 13)
  - Letters (Box 28, Volume 14)
  - Atomic Energy Conference at Chicago, September 19-20, 1945 (Box 28, Volume 15)
  - Material from Congress (Box 28, Volume 16)
  - McMahon Committee, hearings, digests, etc. (Box 28, Volume 17)
  - United Nations organization (Box 28, Volume 18)
  - Pictures (Box 28, Volume 19)
- Series IV: Addenda
  The third series, Library of the ASC, consists of miscellaneous correspondence and printed material. Series IV, Addenda, has been arranged into four subseries that include Atomic Scientists of Chicago, University Office of Inquiry, Associated Scientific Groups, and Conferences. The addenda comprise the years 1945 to 1954, mostly of the periods 1945 to 1947, and with a scattering of 1954 papers, the bulk of which concern the Oppenheimer Case. Except for amplifying the atomic energy conferences, and the material on the Oppenheimer Case, the addenda appear to add little informational value to that contained in the other three series. A similarity of folder headings should enable the user to correlate Series IV with Series' I through III.
  - Subseries 1: Atomic Scientists of Chicago
    - Organization, general (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Organization, meetings (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Organization, committees (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Organization, membership and mailing lists (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Organization, information files (bibliography) (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Organization, information files (Kingdom, Frank, broadcasts, 10-16-45 to 4-4-46) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Organization, information files (Military, political and social aspects of atomic energy -- I [American Association for the United Nations -- Dunn, Frederick S.]) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Organization, information files (Military, political and social aspects of atomic energy -- II [Einstein, Albert -- McCleery, William]) (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Organization, information files (Military, political and social aspects of atomic energy -- III [Pfanstiehl, Alfred -- Weiss, Paul, and anonymous]) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Organization, information files (Polls on atomic energy questions) (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Organization, information files (Technical aspects of atomic energy, general) (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Organization, information files (Technical aspects of atomic energy, Smyth report) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Organization, information files (United Nations and world government -- I (American Association for the United Nations -- Farmer, Fyke) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Organization, information files (United Nations and world government -- II (Primer for Peace, ed. By Norton Gerber for the Association of Oak Ridge Engineers and Scientists, and published by the Association of Scientists for Atomic Education) (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Organization, information files (U.S. Government, documents I [79th Congress, 1st session, bills and resolutions, S1717 to SR107/146]) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Organization, information files (U.S. Government, documents II [79th Congress, 1st session, speeches by U.S. senators, Executive departments, miscellaneous documents] (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Organization, information files (legislative analyses and proposals) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Activities, Bulletin of Atomic Scientists of Chicago (editorial, layout and printing directions, draft articles and editorials, galley proofs and specimen copy) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Activities, Bulletin of Atomic Scientists of Chicago (first issue, distribution of first issue, letters accompanying distribution of first issue, abstracts of responses on receipt of first issue) (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Activities, proposals (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Activities, Oppenheimer Case campaign (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Activities, policy statements (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Activities, press notices, press releases and press conferences (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Activities, legislative campaigns (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Activities, membership polls (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, internal (A-Z by author) (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, outgoing (A-Z by recipient) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, incoming (A-Z by sender) (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Subseries 2: University Office of Inquiry
    - University Office of Inquiry into the Social Aspects of Atomic Energy, organization, activities (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - University Office of Inquiry into the Social Aspects of Atomic Energy, internal correspondence (A-Z by author) (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - University Office of Inquiry into the Social Aspects of Atomic Energy, outgoing correspondence (A-Z by recipient) (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - University Office of Inquiry into the Social Aspects of Atomic Energy, incoming correspondence (A-Z by sender) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 3: Associated Scientific Groups
    - Atomic Science Groups, activities (Assn. Of Los Alamos Scientists, Cambridge Scientists, Manhattan District Scientists, New York Scientists, Oak Ridge Engineers and Scientists, Philadelphia Scientists, Committee for a National Science Foundation, Independent Citizens' Committee of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, Rocket Laboratory Group) (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Atomic Science Federations, activities (Federation of American Scientists) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Atomic Science Federations, activities (Federation of Atomic Scientists) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - General Science Federations, activities (American Assn. for the Advancement of Science) (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - General Science Federations, activities (National Academy of Sciences, Scientists' Committee on Loyalty Problems) (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Publications of Scientific Groups, occasional publications (Assn. of Oak Ridge Scientists at Clinton Laboratories, Oak Ridge Scientists, Northern California Assn. of Scientists, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, Atomic Energy Committee) (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Publications of Scientific Groups, periodical publications, American Association of Scientific Workers (May-June 1945) Association of Los Alamos Scientists (November 20, 1945-January 15, 1946) Association of Manhattan Project (District) Scientists (November 2, 1945; January 9, 1946) Association of Pasadena Scientists (January 15, 1946-February 12, 1946) Association of Philadelphia Scientists (November 13, 1945-December 18, 1945) Chicago Technical Societies Council (February 1946) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Publications of Scientific Groups, periodical publications, National Committee on Atomic Information (March 25, 1946-April 22, 1946) Oak Ridge Engineers and Scientists (January 13, 1946-February 12, 1946) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Press releases of Atomic Science Groups (Assn. of Cambridge Scientists, Federation of Atomic Scientists, National Liaison Committee on Atomic Information) (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence of associated scientific groups, miscellaneous (A-Z by author) (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 4: Conferences
    - Conferences on technical and social aspects of atomic energy, Atomic Energy Control Conference, Chicago, September 1945, participants, agenda, daily summaries of meetings (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Conferences, Atomic Energy Control Conference, Chicago, September 1945, proceedings, book I (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Conferences, Atomic Energy Control Conference, Chicago, September 1945, proceedings, book II (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Conferences, Atomic Energy Control Conference, Chicago, September 1945, collateral documents for discussion by the conference, memoranda and technical background papers for the conference (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Conferences, Atomic Energy Control Conference, New York, October 1945, list of participants Conference on Domestic Legislation, Chicago, December 1945, report of conference Conference on Problems of the Atomic Age, Chicago, February, 1946, program of conference Dublin Conference on World Peace, Dublin, N.H., October 1945, declaration of the conference, NYT, 10-17-45, correspondence on conference Informal Dinner on Atomic Energy, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C., November 29, 1945, participants in the program, summary statement of the discussion Joint conference of the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace and the Federation of Atomic Scientists on the Problems of War and Peace in the Atomic Age, New York, January 1946, program of conference, proceedings Montreaux Conference, Montreaux, France, August 1947, Montreaux Declaration (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Conferences, Rocky Mountain Conference on Atomic Energy, Denver, December 1945, agenda, findings and recommendations Rye Conference on Atomic Energy Control, Rye, New York, October 1945, agenda for discussion, resolution adopted at conference, press release from conference, correspondence relating to conference St. Louis Conference, St. Louis, Missouri, November 1945, background papers, correspondence, proposals and resolutions (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 5: Lester Guttman Papers
    - ASC, general statement of purpose of scientists (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ASC, minutes of executive committee, 1948-1951, members of executive committee, 1949-1954 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ASC, financial statements, 1947-1952 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ASC, memoranda and meeting notices, 1947-1953 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ASC, press releases, 1948-1955 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ASC, appeal to president on nuclear disarmament, recommendations to AEC on security changes, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - ASC, discussion papers, "An appropriate Role for Science in American Policy Making," "National Security in the Hydrogen Age," "Mobilization of Scientific Manpower," "Long Term Prospects for Essential Minerals" (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ASC, misc. correspondence, 1948-1954 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - ASC, correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - ASC, L. Guttman notes (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - ASC, material from various atomic scientists groups (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - ASC, material from various sympathetic groups (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - ASC, U.S. government documents (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - ASC, misc. speeches, statements, and articles by government officials, scientists, and others, 1945-1955 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - FAS, minutes of the council, 1947-1951, 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - FAS, financial reports, membership lists, 1947-1954 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - FAS, reorganization plan, constitution and by-laws, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - FAS, press releases, 1947-1950, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - FAS, memoranda to chapters and members, 1948-1954 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - FAS, membership drives (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - FAS, scientists committee on loyalty and security, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - FAS, misc. members bulletin, 1951-1955 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - FAS, misc. information bulletins, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - FAS, misc. newsletters, 1948-1955 (Box 34, Folder 10)